Oh, yeah. This door got the full monty.
PENNY: Leonard?
- Uh-huh?
(Penny:)What the hell?
- A killer robot. We built it.
- Yeah, well, it almost killed me.
(Sheldon:)If it wanted to kill you, you'd be dead.
So who exactly does it wanna kill?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, are you unaware
of the upcoming...
(Sheldon:)...Southern California Robot
Fighting League Round Robin Invitational?
(Penny:)You know, since I moved last year,
not all my mail has been forwarded.
It's a big deal, heh.
(Howard:)There's an awards banquet
and a dance afterward.
(Howard:)Perhaps you'd like to come with me.
(Howard:)I know the other fellas
would be really excited to see a girl there.
(Penny:)How is it supposed to be a dance
if I'm the only girl?
(Howard:)Well, that may be a slight exaggeration.
(Howard:)You'd be the only doable girl.